《法外情真》前情提要
Previously on The Guardian.
她有个作模特的梦想
So she's got a dream to model,
我不要作那个扼杀她梦想的人
I'm not gonna be the guy who kills it.
马尔科姆说  这么做我也许能发展一番事业
Malcolm says i may have a career doing this...
有什么问题吗
Is this gonna to be a problem?
你把这里都做什么告诉我  就没问题
Not if you tell me everything is going on here.
就是拍照片而已  先生
Just pictures, sir.
我要穿这个吗
Shall I wear this?
这个呢  还是什么都不穿
This? Or nothing?
你在这儿干什么
What are you doing here?
是罗伊  我头撞了一下
...Roy, hit my damn head...
准备偷你妈妈的首饰呢
Tring to steal your mother's jewelry...
罗伊是怎么知道有首饰的
How did Roy know about the jewelry?
是你告诉他的  对不对
You told him didn't you?
真的很对不起
I'm so sorry...
她不是失踪了  爸爸  她是离家出走
She's not missing dad, she ran away.
- 谁是马尔科姆  - 那个摄影师
- Who's Malcolm? - The photographer.
法林先生  她不在这儿
Mr. fallin, she's not here.
我们找到一些女人的照片
We found some pictures of women.
儿童色情片
Child pornography Roey...
你怎么能让香农和这种人单独相处呢
how could you leave Shannon alone with this guy?
都是我的错
It's my fault.
- 如果明天还是没有消息的话  - 她会回来的
- If I don't hear something by tomorrow... - She'll be back.
是劳瑞·绍尔特来了
Oh... it's Laurie Solt.
别  我去跟她谈吧  我去
No, Dad. I'll... I'll talk to her. I'll talk to her.
香农不见了
Shannon's missing.
- 她离家出走了  - 什么时候的事
- She ran away. - When?
- 今天下午的时候  - 为什么当时不给我打电话
- Sometime this afternoon. - Why didn't you call me?
额  我们报警了
Well, we called the police and...
我回办公室申请一下扣押令
I'll go to the office and get an attachment order.
谢利姆斯就可以在她成为
The Sherims Department can start looking for her
失踪人口之前寻找她了
before she becomes a missing person.
太好了  谢谢你  劳瑞
Great. Thanks, Laurie.
- 没事  再见  - 感谢
- Okay. Bye. - Appreciate it.
嗨
Hey.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
你还好吗
You all right?
我头有点昏
A little dizzy.
那你坐下呀
Why don't you sit down?
我得跟罗伊好好谈谈
I gotta talk to Roy.
什么
What?
我需要你送我过去
I'm gonna need a ride.
你不能把这些钱给他
You're not giving him this money.
我别无选择
I'm gonna do whatever I have to.
好了  我们走吧
Okay. Let's go.
两位好啊
Hey, guys.
我刚想打电话给你们问问你们有没有消息呢
I was actually just gonna call you... see if you heard anything.
罗伊  你在做什么
What're you doing, Roy?
我要把以前的东西捐给古德威尔慈善机构
Oh, I'm just taking some old crap to Goodwill.
这么晚了还出去吗
This time of night?
他们在那后面有一个旧物回收箱
They got a drop-off box in the back.
你去哪里  罗伊
Where are you going, Roy?
我欠了别人钱  他们一直在威胁我
Those guys I owe, they keep threatening me.
他们找不到马尔科姆就来找我的麻烦
Now that they can't find Malcolm, it's all on my ass.
你要跑路了吗
You leaving town?
他们给我的期限快到了  但是我没有办法还钱
I'm running outta time here, and I can't find the money.
那你带我去见他们吧
Well, I want you to take me to them.
绝对不行  如果我没有带钱过去
No way. I show up there without that money,
- 这些人会打断我的  - 钱我来还  我还
- those guys are gonna break my... - I'll pay. I'll pay.
那好吧
All right.
第三季  第十七集
法外真情
翻译   马丁   倪
校对  油 球
特效  转轮 枪
你们在这儿等我
Stay here.
我去找他
I'll go find him.
你还好吗
You okay?
我没事
Yeah.
你年轻的时候经常打台球
You used to play pool when you were younger.
上大学的时候  是啊
ln college, yeah.
我们有的时候会一块玩
We oughta play sometime.
马尔科姆已经把钱还了
Malcolm already paid.
- 什么  - 他已经把钱还完了
- What? - He already paid.
我不知道他怎么弄到钱的
I don't know how the hell he got the money.
不  你知道
Yeah, you do.
喂
Hey.
- 不好意思久等了  - 没有关系
- Sorry to keep you waiting. - That's all right.
你跟我来吧
Why don't you come with me?
我们掌握了马尔科姆·里维斯的一些信息
We have some information about Malcolm Reeves...
我们在一个小时之前逮捕了马尔科姆·里维斯
We arrested Malcolm Reeves an hour ago.
香农当时和他在一起吗
Was Shannon with him?
马尔科姆说今天下午香农去过他家
Malcolm says Shannon showed up at his house this afternoon...
他告诉她  他不能和她待在一起
and he told her she wasn't allowed to be around him.
接着他叫了一辆出租车送她离开了
And he called a cab... sent her on her way.
他知道香农现在哪儿吗
Does he know where she is?
他的律师来了  他现在拒绝说话
He's got a lawyer now. He's not talking anymore.
- 这位是艾莉森·斯坎伦  - 你好
- This is Alison Scanlon. - Hi.
她是一名联邦特工  在帮SAFE做事
She's a Federal Agent that works with SAFE.
- 什么是SAEF  - 就是性侵犯重罪执法
- What's that? - Sexual Assault Felony Enforcement.
艾莉森来这里负责调查坎迪斯·布莱尔的案子
Alison came to town on the Candace Bleier case.
谁
Who?
坎迪斯·布莱尔
Candace Bleier.
就是在马尔科姆·里维斯工作室照片里的女孩
The girl in the photos found in Malcolm Reeves' studio.
我已经找了坎迪斯一年多了
I've been trying to find Candace for over a year.
直到今天  我们掌握的资料还只是几段录像
Up until today, all that's surfaced is a few videos.
你觉得香农可能和这个女孩在一块吗
You think Shannon might be with this girl?
如果坎迪斯还活着的话  就有可能
lf Candace is still alive, it's a possibility.
法林先生  仅仅因为马尔科姆·里维斯
Mr. Fallin, just because Malcolm Reeves
有坎迪斯的照片
was in possession of photographs of Candace
并不意味着他抓走了她们
doesn't mean he took them
也不意味着他有做伤害您的养女的事
and doesn't mean he's done anything to your foster child.
这个人是个拍色情片的
The man's a pornographer.
他用一天的时间就拿到了1万美元
He came up with ten thousand dollars in one day.
你觉得他的钱都是哪儿来的
Now where do you think he got that money?
你能帮我们找到香农吗
Can you help us find Shannon?
很难  这些人都居无定所的
It's very hard. These people move around a lot.
一会儿在仓库  一会儿在汽车旅馆  一会儿又在家里了
Operate out of warehouses and motels and homes.
有的时候会住几天  有的时候就待几个小时
Sometimes for days, sometimes just for hours.
好吧  你能不能告诉我  还是有可能找到她的
Well, can you tell me it's not impossible to find her.
他们得把他们的作品卖出去
They do have to sell their product.
这是追踪他们的一个办法
That's one way to track them.
通过他们在互联网或者当地报纸的背面
Through encrypted codes they post on the Internet
发布的加密代码
or in the back of local papers.
如果看到了私人保镖或者按摩的广告  可能就是线索了
Wherever there are personal, escort, or massage ads, there may be leads.
爸
Dad.
法林先生
Mr. Fallin.
利维医生
Dr. Levy.
你父亲的中耳和内耳之间有个不正常的裂口
Your father has an abnormal opening between his middle and inner ear.
这是由于几年前的头部损伤引起的
It's a result of the head injury he received a few days ago.
嗯
Okay.
他有一个很棒的名字  叫外淋巴瘘
It, uh... has a fancy name-- Perilymph Fistula--
但是只是意味着他会有平衡的问题  站不稳
but all that means is that he has a balance disorder. Vertigo.
- 好的  - 现在我们需要他住在医院
- Okay. - Now, we've admitted him for the night,
但是在接下来的一周内  他必须要好好休息
but he'll need strict bed rest for at least a week.
- 好的  - 好吗  不能开车
- Right. - All right? No driving.
不能有压力  不能提重物
No straining or heavy lifting.
周围大气压不能突然改变
No sudden changes in air pressure.
- 尼克  - 爸
- Nick. - Dad.
他们可能找到她了
They may have found her.
法林先生  你需要卧床休息
Mr. Fallin, you need to stay in bed.
在哪里
Where's that?
- 没有  - 没有吗
- Nothing. - No?
没有人看到
No one saw anything.
有人报警了
Somebody called.
是个匿名电话  可能是个恶作剧吧
It's anonymous. Could've been a prank.
到处都是安珀警戒
Amber alerts all over the place.
先生  我们会尽全力找到她的
We'll do everything we can to find her, sir.
好的  谢谢你
All right. Thank you.
你来看看这个
You might want to take a look at this.
斯坎伦小姐  你怎么看
So what do you think, Miss Scanlon?
这和他们的做法很一致
Well, it fits their M.O.
在汽车旅馆开一间很廉价的房间  做一个
Check into a cheap motel. Make a...
什么
What?
做一个录像  拍照片
Make a video. Take photographs.
是啊
Right.
然后他们就走了  什么都没留下
And then they move on. They don't leave much behind.
我们有消息会给你打电话的
So I'll call you when we hear something.
- 谢谢你  - 谢谢
- Thank you. - Thank you.
爸  你还在这里干嘛  我带你回家
What are you doing here, Dad? Let's get you home.
不  不
No, no.
我要跟这边的所有人聊一聊
I'm gonna talk to everyone here.
谢谢  不好意思打扰了
Thank you. Sorry.
- 爸  走吧  - 这是最后一个
- Dad, let's go. - This is the last one.
你好
Hi.
有事吗
Yeah?
我在找我女儿
I'm, uh... Iooking for my daughter.
她今年13岁  她不见了
She's thirteen years old, and she disappeared.
这个旅馆里有人打电话说见过她
Somebody from this motel called and said they'd seen her.
抱歉
Sorry.
走吧  爸  该回家了
Come on, Dad. It's time to go home.
不
No.
你也听到警察说的了  也许这就是个恶作剧
You... you heard the man. He said it was probably a prank.
有人从这里打了电话啊
Somebody made that call from here.
好吧  那我们明天再继续查吧
Right. Well, we'll look into it tomorrow.
我们还是
Let's just...
电话是我打的
I did it.
我打的
I made the call.
你为什么不跟警察说
Why didn't you talk to the police?
因为我女儿跟我在一块  而且我上面还有老板
'Cause I got my daughter and I got priors
警察看到我住在这里会把我的女儿带走的
and the cops are gonna take her away again if they see me living like this.
你知不知道是谁把我女儿抓走了
Do you know who took my daughter away?
知不知道他们去哪儿了
Do you know where they took her?
也许吧
Maybe.
我报警是我有点担心那个头发是金色的女孩
I only called the cops because I was worried about that little blonde girl.
她看起来是个好人
She looked nice.
这是我报警的唯一原因
It's the only reason I called.
听着  你必须把你知道的都告诉警方
Look, you've got to talk to the police.
- 不行  - 那你告诉我吧
- No way. - Well, then tell me.
你想要什么
What do you want?
你想要钱吗  我给你钱
You want money? I'll give you money.
我现在就给你1千美元  拿着
I'll give you a thousand dollars. Take it.
喂  喂
Hey. Hey.
如果你报警的话  我什么都不会告诉你的
You call the cops, I ain't telling you nothing.
那你带我去见她吧
You'll take me to her?
我不能把我女儿丢在这里吧
Can't just leave my girl.
我儿子会照顾她的
My son'll take care of her.
- 能不能慢慢来  - 她会带我去见香农
- Hey, will you slow down? - She'll take me to her.
她是妓女  为了1千美元她什么事都做得出来
She's a prostitute, Dad. She'll do anything for a thousand dollars.
我去  你在这里等着
I'll go. You wait.
我去
I'll go.
不许报警
No cops.
只要一张报纸  密码就在报纸背面
Just need a newspaper. They got codes in the back.
留在这儿别动
Sit tight.
车上有张报纸
There's a paper in the car.
我需要一支笔和一个电话
I need a pen and a phone.
等我一下
Just give me a second.
他们把电话号码藏在了几个广告里
They spread the phone number over a couple ads.
8.
好的  知道啦
Okay. Got it.
嗨
Hey.
Hi.
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
维奥莱特
Violet.
你是谁
Who are you?
我叫伯顿
I'm Burton.
你妈妈的朋友
Friend of your mom's.
你去哪儿
Where are you going?
我会很安静的  先生
I'll be quiet, mister.
你不用坐在衣柜里  亲爱的
You don't have to sit in a closet, honey.
你有吃的吗
You have any food?
没有
No.
在这儿停车
Stop here.
就是这里
This is the place.
从这个门进去  就说你要找达蒙
Just go in that door there and ask for Damon.
告诉他你是朋友
Tell him you're... a friend.
- 你要做什么  - 我不能跟你一起进去
- And what are you gonna do? - Can't go in there with you.
为什么不
Why not?
你告诉他你是嫖客  你要找个漂亮的小姐
Just tell him you're a john. You need a young girl to get off.
把钱准备好
Have your money ready.
你告诉他你要看片儿  你就不用跟她那个了
Just tell him you're a watcher so you don't gotta do nothing with her.
我要回去了
I'm going home.
告诉他你只喜欢看就行了
Just tell him you're a watcher.
以前怎么都没见过你
Never seen you before.
这个嘛  额
Yeah, well, you know...
你怎么知道这儿的
How'd you get here?
我是迪娜的朋友
Friend of Dina's.
好吧  你想要哪种类型的
Okay. What do you want?
额
Uh...
我这里有俊男靓女
I got girls, boys.
儿童色情片  儿童成人片  硬核色情片  亚洲片  性虐片  性虐文学  第一视角A片等等
Kid on kid, adult on kid, hard core, Asian, S&M, S&M Lite, gonzo style,
- 你要的我这里都有  - 我只是来找一个孩子的
- whatever product you want. - I'm just looking for a girl.
- 好吧  什么样的孩子  - 金发  年轻的
- Okay. What kind? - Blonde. Young.
- 青少年吗还是13岁以下的  - 我不知道  我不知道
- Teen? Pre-teen? - I don't know. I don't know.
我喜欢看  我是来看片的
I'm a watcher. I just ... I like to watch.
好吧  楼上有个年轻的金发女孩  刚来没多久
Okay. Well, I got a young blonde upstairs... pretty new.
两千美元
Be two grand.
是的  半小时收费两千美元
Yeah. It's two thousand dollars for half an hour.
坐吧
Take a seat.
好的
Right.
上来吧
Come on up.
对  对  请帮我找一下艾莉森·斯坎伦
Yeah. Yeah. Can I have Alison Scanlon, please?
我们逮捕了那里的所有人
We arrested everybody in the place.
那儿有五个女孩
Five girls in there.
没收了二十几个录像带
Confiscated two dozen tapes.
一晚上看了大部分的证据
Spent the better part of the night going over the evidence.
我们把你们叫过来是因为  有一个录像
The reason we called you in, there's a tape.
这段录像的画质不是很清晰  里面的女孩被下了药
The quality on it isn't very good, and the girl in it is drugged,
但是我们很担心她就是香农
but we're concerned it might be Shannon.
我们需要你们其中的一个确认下
We need one of you to take a look.
爸  让我来吧
You know, Dad, you should just let me do this.
如果是香农  我得知道她经历了什么
lf it's Shannon, I need to know what she's been through.
你很漂亮
Oh, you're pretty.
我喜欢你的头发
I like your hair.
天呐
Good Lord.
别放了
Hey... stop.
什么
What?
能不能回放一下
Can you rewind it?
播放
Press Play.
暂停
Pause it.
好吧  维奥莱特
Okay, Violet.
你到底在干嘛
What the hell are you doing?
我看到录像带了
I saw the tape.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
我在市中心的警察局看到有一个关于香农的录像带
Police Station downtown-- there's a video tape of Shannon.
- 你在录像里  - 我才没有
- You're in it. - I'm not in a tape.
我看到你的影子了  我看到了
I saw your reflection. I saw you.
儿童性虐是二级重罪
Sexual abuse of children's a second degree felony.
至少要坐4年牢
You're looking at four years minimum.
至于维奥莱特  将会交由国家监护
And Violet, she becomes a ward of the State.
我知道了  我知道了
I know. I know.
- 维奥莱特在哪里  - 我在这儿
- Where's Violet? - In here.
没事的  维奥莱特  你出来吧
It's okay, Violet. You can come out.
我没有碰你妹妹
I didn't touch your sister.
我什么都没做  只是做着帮她冷静下来
I didn't do nothing but sit with her and keep her calm.
你知道她在哪儿吗
You know where she is?
我可以再试试
I could try again.
如果你答应我不报警的话  我可以再试试
lf you promise not to call the cops, I could try again.
- 还会像上次那样吗  - 我上次至少带你去了一个真实的地方
- Is this gonna be like last time?  - I took you some place real, didn't l?
我不会再耍你了
I am not trying to play you.
你最好好好想想
Yeah, I think you're gonna try again.
否则我就会跟警察说录像带的事情
Or I can talk to the police about the tape.
我不能保证她一定在那里
I can't promise you she's in there.
我们只是去那里看一下
Just go in there and check.
他们那些人不是总是想看到我的
These guys don't always want me around.
只是有时候他们知道我有办法让新来的女孩子冷静下来
It's just... sometimes... they know I can help them calm down the new girls.
因为我知道怎么劝说  因为我曾经也是新来女孩
'Cause I know how to talk to 'em 'cause... I was a new girl once.
告诉我她在不在里面
Tell me if she's inside.
我没有耍你
I wasn't playing you.
你妹妹的事我很抱歉  因为我也经历过
I felt bad for your sister because I'd been there myself.
嗨
Hi.
你最喜欢什么颜色
What's your favorite color?
我没有最喜欢的颜色
l-- I... I don't really have one.
我喜欢绿色
I like green.
很好  很不错
That's good. That's nice.
真的喜欢
Really.
为什么喜欢绿色
Why is that?
我就是喜欢
I just really like it.
好吧
Right.
她就在里面
She's in there.
谢谢你
Thank you.
快  快  把后面包围起来
Let's hurry it up. Go around back.
警察  所有人蹲下
Police! Everybody get down!
乔纳斯  去后面的房间
Jonas, get the back room!
她样子看上去还不错
She's in pretty good shape, physically.
但是她一直在服用或者被迫服用毒品  所以她看起来有点恍惚
But she's taken or been given drugs, so she's still a little bit out of it.
嗯
Right.
警察明天一早想要找她谈话
The police'll want to see her first thing in the morning.
好吧
Okay.
她有没有
Was, uh...
没有  没事了
No, it's okay.
她没有被强奸
She wasn't raped.
谢天谢地
Thank God.
伯顿  关于香农你需要帮助
Burton, you're gonna need some help dealing with her.
是啊
Yeah.
短期看来  我就告诉她
ln the short term, I'd just tell her
你不会为发生的任何事责怪她
you don't blame her for anything that happened.
不要问太多问题
Don't ask her too many questions.
也不要因为她不听你的话就惩罚她
And don't punish her for disobeying you in the first place.
我给香农推荐了几个好的心理医生
I've got a list of therapists for Shannon.
至于你  如果你想找人谈谈
And one for you, if you want to talk to anybody.
我没事的
Oh, no. I'm fine.
但是  谢谢你  感谢
But thank you. Thank you.
好吧
Okay.
我去看看是不是快要放她走了
I'll go see if they're ready to release her.
好的
Okay. Good.
非常感谢
Thank you very much.
他什么时候来的
When'd he get here?
大概十分钟之前
About ten minutes ago.
很高兴他们找到了她  对吧
I'm glad they found her, huh?
- 法林先生  我  - 你别管了
- Mr. Fallin, l, uh... - You should've stayed away.
她是我的孩子啊
She's my kid.
你真的别管了
You should've stayed away.
我没有想到这样的事会发生在她身上  先生
I never meant for anything to happen to her, sir.
香农
Shannon.
嗨
Hey.
没事的  香农
It's okay, Shannon.
一切都会好起来的
It's gonna be all right.
你跟伯顿走吧
you gotta go with Burton.
好吗
Okay?
对不起
I'm sorry.
香农  你能不能告诉我们你和马尔科姆·里维斯的关系
Shannon, can you tell us about your relationship with Malcolm Reeves?
马尔科姆是个摄影师
Malcolm is a photographer.
然后呢
Okay.
他说我可以成为一名模特
He... said I could be a model.
马尔科姆有没有碰过你
Did Malcolm ever touch you?
他有没有脱过你的衣服
Did he ever ask you to take your clothes off?
没有
No.
你父亲说你在去马尔科姆的工作室之前有给他打过电话
Your father said you called and said you were going to Malcolm's studio.
是的  他告诉我不要去  让我回家
I did... and he told me to go home.
他给我叫了出租车让我走
He called me a cab and told me to go.
你上车了吗
Did you get into a cab?
是个面包车
It was like a van.
我想我可能在车子后面睡着了
I think I just... I fell asleep in the back.
马尔科姆在车上吗
Was Malcolm in the van with you?
不在
No.
你还记得什么
What else do you remember?
我不知道
I don't know.
感觉我睡了很久
It was like I slept for a long time.
我记得我当时在房间看电视
I remember watching television somewhere in this house,
然后我记得警察进来了
and then I remember the police coming in.
你记不记得这两天之前发生的事情
Do you remember anything about the last two days?
不记得了
No.
香农  记不记得有个录像带
Shannon, there's a tape.
我真的不记得了  好吗
I don't really remember, okay?
你不记得被带到一个汽车旅馆吗
You don't remember being taken to a motel room?
我说了我不记得任何事了
I said I don't remember anything.
香农  亲爱的
Shannon... honey.
跟斯坎伦说实话
Tell Miss Scanlon the truth.
我说的就是实话
I am.
我说的就是实话啊
I am telling her the truth.
我们应该明天再聊
Maybe we should talk again tomorrow.
好吧
That's fine.
谢谢你  香农
Thank you, Shannon.
劳瑞  给我一点时间  好吗
Laurie, uh, give me a minute, will you?
我在外面等你
I'll be right out.
很显然  她在录像带里被下药了
She's clearly drugged on the tape.
有没有可能这两天她服用了镇定剂
Could be she was sedated for the last few days
或者是她不想聊而已
or she just might not want to talk about it.
所以你打算要怎么办
So what're you gonna do?
迪娜  那个我们抓到的妓女  不肯说话
Dina, the prostitute we arrested, isn't talking.
如果香农不合作的话  我们也无能为力
lf Shannon doesn't cooperate, we can't do much.
马尔科姆呢
And Malcolm?
他今天早上被保释了
He made bail this morning.
我们只能告他持有儿童色情读物
We've got him on a possession of child pornography charge.
我们目前只能做这些
That's all we can do for now.
嗨
Hey.
嗨  香农怎么样了
Hey. How's Shannon?
我不知道  她
Uh... I don't know, she's...
伯顿怎么样了
What about Burton?
他没事
He's fine.
你知道的  我  我收集了一些信息
Well, you know, l, uh... I put together some information.
合适的话  我可以把这些交给他
When-- when you think it's appropriate, I can send it over to him.
太好了  谢谢  我来给他吧
Great. Thanks. I'll-- I'll pass it on to him.
好的
Uh... okay.
你今晚有安排吗
You busy tonight?
没有
I don't have any plans, no.
太好了  因为我想带你去个地方
Great, 'cause I'd like to take you someplace.
去哪儿
Where?
我要给你一个惊喜
It's a surprise.
- 什么意思  - 晚点我来接你
- What do you mean? - l-- I'll pick you up later here.
尼克
Nick...
维奥莱特怎么样了
How's Violet doing?
她基本上没说话
She doesn't seem to like talking much.
但是据我观察  她应该没有去上幼儿园
But from what I can tell, she never went to kindergarten, preschool, nothing.
她就每天待在汽车旅馆
She just, uh, sat around in her motel room all day.
是啊
That's right.
你好  维奥莱特
Hey, Violet.
你还记得我吗
Do you remember me?
我会帮你找个地方暂时住在那里  好吗
I'm gonna help to find you a nice place to stay for a while, okay?
怎么会有人没有最喜欢的颜色呢
How come you don't have a favorite color?
我不知道
Uh... I... I don't know.
每个人都有自己最喜欢的颜色啊
Everyone has a favorite color.
紫色吧
Violet.
什么
What?
紫色  紫色挺好的
Violet. Seems like a nice color.
别逗了
Shut up.
- 亲爱的  听着  - 我要看电影了
- Honey, listen... - I'm gonna watch television.
香农  听着
Shannon, look... listen, uh...
我去咨询了下  想给你提供一些帮助
I talked to some people about getting you some help.
有位女医生很不错
There's this one lady who evidently is very good.
她帮助过很多孩子
She's done a lot of work with kids
经历过这些的   也就是你经历的这些
who've... been through what you've been through,
所以  我让劳瑞请她过来
and... so l, uh... asked Laurie to... to bring her over here.
什么时候
When?
一小时之内
ln about, uh, about an hour.
我没事  伯顿  我不需要找人聊
I'm fine, Burton. I don't have to talk to anybody.
- 亲爱的  听着  - 我没事  伯顿  好吗
- Honey, look... - I'm fine, Burton, okay?
香农  事实就是  我自己可能需要帮助
Shannon... the fact is l, uh... I probably need a little help myself.
随便吧
Whatever.
好无聊
I'm bored.
你的社会工作人员要和阿尔文为你完成一些书面材料
Your social worker just has to finish up some paperwork with Alvin.
- 画的不错  - 我画的是你
- Now that's good. - It's you.
你真好
That's very nice.
谢谢
Thank you.
你有电视吗
You got a TV?
没有  这里没有
No, not here.
我是尼克·法林
Nick Fallin.
劳瑞·绍尔特和一位辅导员今天过来和我们聊了聊
You know, Laurie Solt came over to talk to us with a... a counselor.
哦
Right.
香农说她去楼上看电视
Shannon says she'd be up in her room watching TV.
她们到了之后我上楼叫她
They got here, and I go upstairs.
- 她不在楼上了  - 她走了吗
- She's not there. - She's gone?
我没有听到她离开
I didn't hear her leave.
- 你报警了吗  - 没有  我没必要报警
- Did you call the police? - No, I didn't have to.
劳瑞·绍尔特很生气
Laurie Solt-- she was angry.
她跟我说我再也管不住香农了
Told me she didn't think I could handle Shannon anymore.
也许她说得对
Maybe she's right.
也许我应付不了了
Maybe I can't handle all this...
胡说八道
That's crap.
你不用自责
You can't blame yourself.
你好
Hello.
好  罗伊
Yeah. Roy.
嗯  好的
Yeah. Okay.
好的
Sure.
罗伊现在陪着香农在马尔科姆的工作室
Roy's with Shannon at Malcolm's studio.
亲爱的  你还好吗
Honey, you all right?
我  我需要你的帮助
l-- I need your help.
- 怎么了  - 我们进去谈吧
- What's going on? - I need to talk to you inside.
到底怎么了
What's going on here?
我陪着她
I'll stay with her.
要不要坐到车上
You want to sit in the car?
我接到了马尔科姆的电话说香农又到他的工作室了
So I get this call from Malcolm, and he says that Shannon's back here
他想让她离开  因为她给他添了很多麻烦
and he... wants her out because of all the trouble she causes him.
我开车过来的时候  一路上我都在想  是香农给他造成麻烦了吗
I drive over, the whole time thinking, ''The trouble she caused him?''
所以我进来之后  让香农到外面等我
So I come in here. I tell her to wait outside.
我问他做了些什么
Asked him what he did it for.
他跟我撒谎
He just lied.
我问他钱是哪里来的
I asked him where he got the money.
他撒谎
He lied.
所以我朝他开了枪
So I shot him.
我开了两枪
Twice.
他错了太多
After what he did...
罗伊会怎么样
What's gonna happen to Roy?
我不知道啊  亲爱的
I don't know, honey.
他会不会进监狱
He's going to jail?
目前会
For the time being, yeah.
马尔科姆说等我长大了他会娶我
Malcolm told me he'd marry me when I got old enough.
是吗
Really?
他说我们可以搬到纽约  或者洛杉矶或者  巴黎去
He said we could move somewhere like... New York or Los Angeles... or Paris.
是吗
Right.
他一直说他很爱我
He said he loved me... all the time.
他一直这样跟我说
He would say that all the time.
但是当我到今天那里的时候  他吼了我
But then... when I got over there... he yelled at me.
骂我  说我给他惹了很多麻烦
Called me names. Told me I got him into trouble.
但是  这些都是他让我做的呀
But, he's... he's the one who wanted me to do all that stuff.
嗯
Yeah.
他拍的那些照片还有汽车旅馆的那些录像
The pictures he took and the tape at the motel...
我都记得的  伯顿
I remember it, Burton.
我只是
I just...
我全都记得
I remember all of it.
但是我答应过马尔科姆我不会告诉别人
I just promised Malcolm I'd never tell.
维奥莱特的养父母来接她了
Violet's foster parents are here to pick her up.
谢谢
Thanks.
你准备好了吗
You ready?
我有点害怕
Little bit scared?
没事的
That's okay.
如果你需要我帮忙的话就给我打电话  好吗
lf you need anything... anything at all, you just call me, okay?
好的
Okay.
这是送你的新家的礼物
It's for your new house.
世界上的每种颜色都在里面了
It's every color in the world.
哇  谢谢
Oh. Thanks.
嗨  听我说  昨晚的事我很抱歉
Hey, uh... Look, I'm sorry about last night.
我明白  你不用道歉  没事
I understand. You don't have to apologize. It's okay.
你现在在干嘛
What're you doing right now?
没什么
You know... the usual.
拿上外套  我想给你看样东西
Grab your coat. I want to show you something.
你把房子买下了吗
You bought the house?
我只是付了定金
Well, I just... put down a deposit.
- 尼克  - 不  只是
- Nick... - No. It's just...
有很多问题要考虑  那样不太安全
you know, there's so much... that's just not safe,
而且你知道的  很多事都不太行
and, uh... you know, so much that doesn't work and...
是  但是  尼克
Yeah, but, Nick...
我想让你住到一个安全的地方
I want to know that you live somewhere good.
一个安全的地方
Somewhere... safe.
你和孩子
Both you and the baby.
所以我希望你能住在这里
So, uh... I want you to have it.
有我或者没我都行  我想让你住在这里
With or without me, l... I want you to have it.
我要和你在一起
With you.
但是不是像这样
But not like this.
那你想怎么样都好
Then however you want.
我是说  我
I mean, I...
很感谢为我做的这些
Thank you so much... for doing this.
但是  我觉得啊
But, I... I don't know, I think that, you know,
现在我们应该把心思放在一些小事上面
for now we should probably just work on the little things.
小事
The little things?
对
Right.
小事
The little things.
亲爱的
Honey...
一切都会好起来的  亲爱的
everything's gonna work out just fine, honey.
他们找了最专业的人来帮你
They got the best people to help you.
一切都会好起来的
Everything's gonna be just fine.
待会你进去后  慢慢跟他们说
Now, when you go in there, just... take your time.
说详细一点
Slow and easy.
把你知道的都说出来
Tell them whatever you can.
如果你不想说了  你告诉我  好吗
lf you want to stop... you just let me know, okay?
等这些结束了  所有的事都回归正轨
When this is all over and everything gets back to normal,
我们再谈收养的事
we'll... get the adoption going again.
罗伊的事我很难过
I feel bad for Roy.
罗伊会理解的
Well, Roy understands.
他毕竟是我爸爸啊  伯顿
He's my dad, Burton.
我真的很难过
I just feel bad for him.
我们待会儿再谈这件事好吗
Well... Iook, we'll talk about this Iater, okay?
好的
Right.
- 准备好了吗  - 好了
- Ready? - Yeah.
好的
Okay.
她还好吗
How is she?
在睡觉
Sleeping.
她有没有把知道的都告诉警察
Did she tell the police everything?
都说了
Oh... yeah.
你知道吗  如果我是罗伊  我也会这么做的
You know, if I were Roy... I would've done the same thing.
如果我先到了那里  我也会做同样的事
lf I'd gotten over there first, I'd have done the same thing.
她  呃
She, uh...
她不想让我收养她了
she doesn't want me to adopt her anymore.
为什么
Why is that?
她很担心罗伊  说她自己不属于这里
She's worried about Roy, and she says she doesn't belong here.
也许她说得对
Maybe she's right.
也许是我太着急想成为
Maybe I... just tried too damn hard to be...
那个不是自己的自己了
be something that I really am not.
你做的这些
What you did, son.
谢谢你做的这一切
Thank you for what you did.
爸  我没做什么事
Dad, I... I didn't do anything.
你是个好男人  尼古拉斯
You're a good man, Nicholas.
晚安
Good night.
你不用在这里陪着我
You don't have to stay here on my account.
我没事的
I'll be all right.
Xgun擦枪小组 有偿招募译制成员 诚邀阁下
加入Q群：545053435
请注明职务：翻译、听译、aegisub特效（熟练手）
对字幕有任何意见和建议的同学请加Q群：544487177